<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:55:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Car make reliability comparison</title><link>/posts/car-make-reliability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:55:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/car-make-reliability/</guid><description>Like many other countries, Finland mandates annual car inspections, and unlike other countries, also publishes this data. It aggregates inspection failure data per (make+model, year) and reports average and median odometer reading (i.e. distance driven).
We can therefore plot this data and try to draw our own conclusion. We plot cars produced since 2014 (ten years ago), where each dot represents a different (model, year) tuple, and additionally fit a linear regression line.</description></item><item><title>Some formatting tests</title><link>/posts/formatting-tests/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:58:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/formatting-tests/</guid><description>Images Footnotes! Math Some More Subtrees! Tables Tabs Text flow (lipsum) Images We can attach images to the org heading, we just have to make sure
We can even make it textwidth
Note that we have set org-export-with-tags to nil to not include the tag in the headline.
Footnotes! Here goes a footnote1. Notice that if we call this heading &amp;ldquo;Footnotes&amp;rdquo; there is a problem.
Math Here are some inline equations $ ∫_a^b x dx $ and some block equations:</description></item><item><title>My first org post</title><link>/posts/my-first-org-post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 22:59:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/my-first-org-post/</guid><description>This is my first subheading. This is my post body
This is my first subheading. Have you ever tried to create a subheading? Because I have!</description></item><item><title>Commute times in Zürich</title><link>/posts/commute-times-in-zurich/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/commute-times-in-zurich/</guid><description>A recent article in the &amp;ldquo;Neue Züricher Zeitung&amp;rdquo; claims that Zürich public transport is &amp;ldquo;only&amp;rdquo; about twice the walking speed, and slower than biking.
To make up my own mind, I have evaluated some of my common trips for all three modes of transportation, using google maps. Note that some trips start with &amp;ldquo;bike&amp;rdquo;, which is me biking to the train station, which saves about 6 minutes. I have recorded it as I typically travel &amp;ndash; e.</description></item><item><title/><link>/posts/all-posts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/all-posts/</guid><description>TODO Why not a flywheel? Motivation Energy storage is becoming increasingly important. Current solutions include batteries water storage connected grid fuel? Why not a flywheel? A flywheel can also be used for energy storage.
Essentially, take a wheel and start spinning it when energy is cheap. When you need the energy again, use a generator, i.e., electric motor, to get energy back.
How large would a flywheel need to be? Let us imagine a world where each household has a flywheel in the basement1 that aims to provide one full day of energy.</description></item></channel></rss>